<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Gatsby Starter Blog RSS Feed]]></title><description><![CDATA[Privacy, Open Source Software, Bitcoin, and Monero]]></description><link>https://github.com/wanderingmud1D9</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 02:35:14 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title><![CDATA[Instantiating a new blog]]></title><description><![CDATA[Hello everyone. This blog is to serve as a publishing platform through which I
am able to readily advocate for the usage of open source…]]></description><link>https://github.com/wanderingmud1D9/12-31-2021/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://github.com/wanderingmud1D9/12-31-2021/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Dec 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Hello everyone. This blog is to serve as a publishing platform through which I
am able to readily advocate for the usage of open source privacy technologies,
Bitcoin, and Monero.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While I am going to attempt to refrain from engaging in political discourse
(this is reserved for a separate, but related, blog), there are perhaps a few
essential points which it might be best to clarify:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I fully and actively support the right of all citizens to freedom from
surveillance by state and federal governments. Additionally, this often times
intersects with advocating against the usage of products and services offered by
multinational corporations. This includes (particularly now), the right to
privacy regarding one’s own medical history. No institution or organization
should be endowed with the authority to mandate medical procedures for any citizen.
Records of the medical histories of citizens should also, obviously, never be
used to restrict one’s freedom of movement.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I assert that the right to property is essential to the survival of
sovereignty at the level of each individual citizen. As such, I am wholly and
entirely opposed to Marxism, state-collectivism, and most leftist-inspired social
philosophies. There may be few exceptions regarding possible tolerance for left-wing
market anarchism, but I simply not well-versed enough in these movements to comment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The right to self-defense (including the ability to bear any and all means of
defending oneself, innocent members of a community, or private property) is
also a right I consider to be critical to full citizen sovereignty.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Western civilization has yielded extremely bountiful and beautiful works of
art, literature, philosophical traditions, and aesthetic movements. The
preservation and protection of these (along with those innocent citizens of
the western world) is sacrosanct.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you very much for your interest, and I look forward to future posts addressing
technical topics.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>